http://www.datarecoverylabs.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Datarecoverylabs.com does not rent, sell, or disclose any user information, and abides by the most stringent confidentiality practices.
We are always fully devoted to preserving the privacy of all of our clients and the information they share with us.  Our Privacy Policy demonstrates our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our customers.
What information do we collect from you and why?
At the time you submit your request, or send us a page, we collect the data you provide such as your contact information.  This data is used by us solely to contact you and to respond to your inquiry and questions.
At Datarecoverylabs.com we are committed to protecting your privacy online. We use the information that we collect about our customers to fulfill product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience.
When you shop with Datarecoverylabs.com, we collect transactional information, or Personally Identifiable Information, from you such as your name, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, or shipping address. Datarecoverylabs.com does not sell or rent your transactional information to others. Datarecoverylabs.com uses customer information only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, and enhancing the user experience.
Datarecoverylabs.com may disclose your information to authorized governing agencies if we are legally bound to do so, or for fraud prevention purposes, or to protect ourselves, our customers, and the general public.
Security
At Datarecoverylabs.com you can be assured that your transactional information is secure, consistent with current industry standard SSL encryption technology. The importance of security for all transactional information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. Our secure servers protect the information using state of the art firewall technology. All customer transactional account information is kept on a secure server.  We feel confident in making this guarantee because our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal data including your name and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. You can tell when you are protected by encryption - the lock or key at the bottom of your browser changes color or is no longer broken. To use this option, you must have a browser that supports SSL (ex. Microsoft Internet Explorer, AOL, or Netscape Navigator).
Please, remember to close your browser window when your transaction is complete as this will keep your account safe if you use your computer in a public place like an office or library.
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Services
RAID Data Recovery
Hard Drive Recovery
SSD Recovery
Desktop Recovery
Copyright © 2020 DataRecoveryLabs.com. All Rights Reserved.
